(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,r){},12:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(1),n=r.n(s),a=r(5),o=r.n(a),i=(r(11),r(3)),c=r(2),w=r(6),l=[{questionText:"Which grammar causes recursive-descent parser to go into infinite loop?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"LL(1)",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Left Recursive Grammer",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Right Recursive Grammer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Grammer with left factors",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"A rightmost derivation in reverse can be obtained by",answerOptions:[{answerText:"prefixing",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Handle pruning",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Reduction",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Shifting",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of the following phases is accessed by almost all phases of compiler?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Symbol Table",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Scanner",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Code Generator",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Parser",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Data flow engines generate",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Code generator",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Syntax Analyzer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Specification of tokens",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:" Code Optimizer",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"The most powerful LR Parser is",answerOptions:[{answerText:"LALR",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"LL(1)",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"CLR",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"SLR",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"YACC is a",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Lexical analyzer generator",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Semantic analyzer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Parser generator",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Code generator",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"In a compiler, grouping of characters into tokens is done by",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Parser",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Scanner",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Code optimizer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Code generator",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Peep - hole optimization is a form of",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Constant folding",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Loop optimization",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Local optimization",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Data flow analysis",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Three address code involves",answerOptions:[{answerText:"At the most of 3 addresses",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Exactly 3 addresses",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"greater than or equal to three addresses",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"No unary operators",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Type checking is normally done during",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Code optimization",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Lexical Analysis",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Syntax analysis",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Syntax Directed Translation",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"S -> (L) | a L -> L, S | S Find the FOLLOW(L)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"{ (}",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"{) }",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"{(,)}",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"{$,',)}",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"One of the implementations of Three address statements is",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Indirect triples",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Postfix Notation",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Syntax Trees",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Three address code",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"In Static allocation, the position of an activation record in memory is fixed at",answerOptions:[{answerText:"program coding",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"compile time",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"program loading",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"execution time ",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which storage allocation strategy manages the run time storage",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Stack Allocation",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Static Allocation",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Heap Allocation",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Linking and Loading",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of the following is considered as a sequence of characters in a token",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Mexeme",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Pattern",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Lexeme",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Texeme",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of the following phase gives tokens as output",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Intermediate code generation",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Lexical analyzer",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Syntax analyzer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Semantic analyzer",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Macro expansion type parameter passing is otherwise called as",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Call - by value",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Call - by reference",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Copy - restore",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Call - by name",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"A basic block can be analyzed by",answerOptions:[{answerText:"a DAG",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"a graph withcycles",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Flow graph",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Constant folding",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Substitution of values for names whose values are constant is done in",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Local optimization",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Constant folding",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Loop optimization",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Data flow analysis",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of the following implementations of three address codes occupy less space",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Quadruples",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Syntax tree",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Triples",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Indirect triples",isCorrect:!1}]}],T=[{questionText:"ICDWA",answerOptions:[{answerText:"New York",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"London",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Paris",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Dublin",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is CEO of Tesla?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Jeff Bezos",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Elon Musk",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Bill Gates",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tony Stark",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The iPhone was created by which company?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Apple",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Intel",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Amazon",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Microsoft",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How many Harry Potter books are there?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"1",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"6",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"7",isCorrect:!0}]}],x=[{questionText:"DAA",answerOptions:[{answerText:"New York",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"London",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Paris",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Dublin",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is CEO of Tesla?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Jeff Bezos",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Elon Musk",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Bill Gates",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tony Stark",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The iPhone was created by which company?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Apple",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Intel",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Amazon",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Microsoft",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How many Harry Potter books are there?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"1",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"6",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"7",isCorrect:!0}]}],C=[{questionText:"CN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"New York",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"London",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Paris",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Dublin",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is CEO of Tesla?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Jeff Bezos",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Elon Musk",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Bill Gates",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tony Stark",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The iPhone was created by which company?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Apple",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Intel",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Amazon",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Microsoft",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How many Harry Potter books are there?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"1",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"6",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"7",isCorrect:!0}]}],u=[{questionText:"SE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"New York",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"London",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Paris",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Dublin",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is CEO of Tesla?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Jeff Bezos",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Elon Musk",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Bill Gates",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tony Stark",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The iPhone was created by which company?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Apple",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Intel",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Amazon",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Microsoft",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How many Harry Potter books are there?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"1",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"6",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"7",isCorrect:!0}]}],m=[{questionText:"WP",answerOptions:[{answerText:"New York",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"London",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Paris",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Dublin",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is CEO of Tesla?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Jeff Bezos",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Elon Musk",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Bill Gates",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tony Stark",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"The iPhone was created by which company?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Apple",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Intel",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Amazon",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Microsoft",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"How many Harry Potter books are there?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"1",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"6",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"7",isCorrect:!0}]}];function p(){var e=Object(s.useState)(null),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),r=t[0],a=t[1],o=Object(s.useState)(0),p=Object(i.a)(o,2),d=p[0],h=p[1],f=Object(s.useState)(!1),b=Object(i.a)(f,2),y=b[0],g=b[1],O=Object(s.useState)(0),E=Object(i.a)(O,2),q=E[0],k=E[1];return r?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},n.a.createElement("button",{type:"reset",id:"home",onClick:function(){return window.location.reload()}},n.a.createElement(w.a,null)),y?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",q," out of ",r.length):n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},n.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",d+1),"/",r.length),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},r[d].questionText)),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},r[d].answerOptions.map((function(e){return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return!0===e.isCorrect&&k(q+1),void(d+1<r.length?h(d+1):g(!0))}},e.answerText))}))))):n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("h1",null,n.a.createElement("i",null,"Choose a subject")),n.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",className:"subject",disabled:!0,onClick:function(){return a(u)}},"Software Engineering ",n.a.createElement(c.a,{style:{marginLeft:"35%"}})),n.a.createElement("br",null),n.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",className:"subject",disabled:!0,onClick:function(){return a(x)}},"Algorithms ",n.a.createElement(c.a,{style:{marginLeft:"62%"}})),n.a.createElement("br",null),n.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",className:"subject",disabled:!0,onClick:function(){return a(C)}},"Computer Networks ",n.a.createElement(c.a,{style:{marginLeft:"38%"}})),n.a.createElement("br",null),n.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",className:"subject",disabled:!0,onClick:function(){return a(m)}},"Web Programming ",n.a.createElement(c.a,{style:{marginLeft:"42%"}})),n.a.createElement("br",null),n.a.createElement("button",{type:"submit",className:"subject",onClick:function(){return a(l)}},"Compiler Design"),n.a.createElement("br",null),n.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",className:"subject",disabled:!0,onClick:function(){return a(T)}},"Indian Constitution ",n.a.createElement(c.a,{style:{marginLeft:"40%"}})),n.a.createElement("p",null,n.a.createElement("i",null,"rest of the subjects to be unlocked soon")),n.a.createElement("a",{href:"https://t.co/NnzHqWoGp4?amp=1"},n.a.createElement("p",{className:"pride"},"Enjoyed em Let's ",n.a.createElement("a",{href:"https://t.co/NnzHqWoGp4?amp=1\r\n"}," Connect \ud83e\udd1e"))))}o.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(p,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2d46a49a.chunk.js.map